



ABOUT

Self-taught developer and indiscriminate fan of all things Javascript.

Experience across the stack with a refined talent for pixel-perfect design implementation and animations. Cyclist, film photographer, rock climber, freelancer, and former builder of buildings.

ы

TECHNOLOGIES

LIBRARIES SERVICES

React/Redux AWS S3, Cloudfront
Gatsby AWS Lambda, API Gateway
Vue AWS EC2, RDS, Elastic Beanstalk
Express Google Cloud Platform

Serverless MongoDB
Sass/Stylus Postgres
Styled Components Heroku
Apollo/GraphQL Netlify

ESLint/Prettier
Webpack



O

EDUCATION

BACHELORS OF SCIENCE

Building Construction

Auburn University 2009 Cum Laude



EXPERIENCE

INBOXLAB

Senior Frontend Developer 01/2019 – PRESENT Frontend Developer 11/2017 – 01/2019

Typical stack includes MongoDB, Express, React, and Node.

- · Launched 6 brands in first 5 months as sole frontend developer
- Authored automatic (device-based) image resizer Lambda function
- · Assembled NPM library for shared internal components/helpers
- Full DevOps responsibilities

Proudly built/actively supporting the following flagship brands:

- The Discoverer (thediscoverer.com)
- Travel Trivia (traveltrivia.com)
- · Seeqr (seeqr.com)
- Trivia Daily (<u>triviadaily.com</u>)
- Trip Trivia (triptrivia.com)
- Trivia Genius (triviagenius.com)

PEACHDISH

Full-Stack Developer 02/2017 – 11/2017

- Play Framework (Java) with Scala and React frontend
- Full-stack responsibilities including DevOps
- Heavy CMS utilization (Prismic) including a completely dynamic landing page creator
- Standards implementation including BEM methodology and global SVG spritesheet builder
- · Active role in UX and UI for improving existing features and new builds

HOLDER CONSTRUCTION

VDC Project Manager 07/2015 - 02/2017 VDC Senior Engineer 07/2012 - 07/2015 VDC Engineer 02/2010 - 07/2012 VDC Office Engineer 08/2009 - 02/2010

Lead VDC Project Manager on Mercedes-Benz Stadium from 11/2013 to 02/2017. Responsible for all BIM execution including 240+ 3D models between design team, subcontractors, and vendors.